<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>a John Friel website</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on a John Friel website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Shiny App to Enhance my Favorite TV Show</title>
      <link>/2018/02/10/shiny-app-to-enhance-my-favorite-tv-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/02/10/shiny-app-to-enhance-my-favorite-tv-show/</guid>
      <description>Enhancing Shark Tank &amp;ndash; Net Worth Compare Tool At some point in an episode of Shark Tank I end up thinking: &amp;ldquo;Well Mark Cuban is worth 3 billion so this deal is the equivalent of me investing 15 dollars.&amp;rdquo; I use estimates and never fully know what each Shark is worth. It also depends on how much the end user is worth. If my parents were to have the same thought, a 200 thousand dollar investment from Cuban, might be similar to a 30 dollar investment from my parents due to higher net worth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>StockScrapeR</title>
      <link>/2018/01/29/stockscraper/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/01/29/stockscraper/</guid>
      <description>knitr::opts_chunk$set(echo = TRUE) library(tidyverse) library(rvest) library(plyr) #devtools::install_github(&amp;quot;wch/webshot&amp;quot;) library(webshot)  Scan Stock Market With Rvest and Webshot problem I wanted a way to look at stocks charts that quickly fit the range of investment I was looking to make.
Let&amp;rsquo;s Grab all Stocks on the NYSE The following script will run rvest on a loop, each loop opens a new webpage. so the first run through opens eoddata.com/stocklist/NYSE/a.htm then grabs all stock information for Stock Tickers beginning with the letter A.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heisman</title>
      <link>/2017/10/29/heismaninfo-rmd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/10/29/heismaninfo-rmd/</guid>
      <description>ghfghfg</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Make an R Powered Custom Visual</title>
      <link>/2017/10/04/how-to-make-an-r-powered-custom-visual/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/10/04/how-to-make-an-r-powered-custom-visual/</guid>
      <description>Power BI Custom VisualsThis is a walkthrough on creating custom visuals for Power BI, specifically, R powered custom Visuals. The end product will be similar to the custom visuals found here.
By the end of this tutorial we will have the following Plotly Scatter 3D chart–fully interactive in Power BI as a custom visual.
## Warning: package &amp;#39;bindrcpp&amp;#39; was built under R version 3.3.3{&#34;x&#34;:{&#34;layout&#34;:{&#34;margin&#34;:{&#34;b&#34;:40,&#34;l&#34;:60,&#34;t&#34;:25,&#34;r&#34;:10},&#34;scene&#34;:{&#34;xaxis&#34;:{&#34;title&#34;:&#34;Weight&#34;},&#34;yaxis&#34;:{&#34;title&#34;:&#34;Gross horsepower&#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Highly analytical and process oriented data analyst with 5+ years of experience. Aiming to utilize my strong sales experience and analytical ability to achieve the goals of your company. Double major from Penn State University with a Master&amp;rsquo;s degree from Southern Methodist in Business Analytics. Excellent Power BI skills. Three years experience in R and SQL.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>